Guide to the William J. Baumol Papers, 1928-2013 and undated RL.00092
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Service, 1942-2010 and undated
  - Legal Testimony, 1958-2006 and undated; 3
    - United States of America v. CBS Inc. and United States v. American Broadcasting Companies Inc., 1980 (Box 68)
    - United States v. ATT, 1981 (Box 68)
    - Warhol Case, 1993; undated; 3 folders (Box 68)
      Includes files related to appraisal of Warhol's works
    - Warhol Case, 1990 (Box 83)
      Includes files related to appraisal of Warhol's work
- Research and Notes, 1953-2012 and undated
  Includes Baumol's notes and correspondence for research projects, and a portion of his collection of academic writings by others. Research notes include files on Baumol's work on anti-trust policy, the theory of fairness, the cost disease, contestable markets, entrepreneurship, economics and education, history of economic thought, innovation and technological progress, industrial organization, economics of the performing arts, and productivity growth, among other topics. Additional correspondence can be found in the Correspondence and Writings series.
  - Research, 1953-2012 and undated; 1
    This subseries contains documents for Baumol's research projects arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 72 Countries, undated (Box 26)
      Includes data on productivity for various countries
    - aDvANCE Project, 2001-2004; 9 folders (Box 28)
      Includes materials for project on careers and retirements of professional dancers
    - aDvANCE Project, 2004 (Box 81)
    - Air Quality, 2007 (Box 26)
    - AMA Survey on Downsizing, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Anti-trust Guidelines, 1985-2000; 2 folders (Box 28)
      Includes readings and materials on antitrust rules and regulations
    - Applied Theory of Fairness, 1980-1983 (Box 28)
      Includes materials for research on making the theory of fairness applicable to policy issues
    - Argentine Telecom, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Art Prices, 1974-2005; 3 folders (Box 28)
      Includes research materials on prices in art markets
    - Beethoven, 1997 (Box 26)
      Includes research materials on Beethoven and performing arts
    - BLS Data, 2002 (Box 26)
      Includes printouts of Bureau of Labor Statistics data on employment and wages
    - Capitalist Growth Machine, 2002 (Box 26)
      Includes hand-written notes and newspaper articles
    - Chaos, 1976-1986 (Box 79)
    - China, 2000-2011; 4 folders (Box 28)
      Includes material for research on China's economic growth
    - China, 2007-2009; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Comparative Statics, undated (Box 79)
    - Computer Prices, 1987 (Box 25)
      Research materials on computer prices
    - Contestable Markets, 1981-1990 (Box 23)
      Includes research materials
    - Contestable Markets, 1987-1996 (Box 25)
      Research materials on contestable markets
    - Convergence, 1964-1986; 3 folders (Box 13)
      Includes research materials on international convergence
    - Convergence, 1990-1998; 3 folders (Box 23)
      Includes research materials on growth, productivity, and international convergence
    - Convergence Hypothesis, 1997 (Box 32)
      Research materials on international productivity convergence
    - Cookbook for NSF/DSI, 1976 (Box 76)
    - Corporate profit datasets, 1989; 5 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0002)
    - Cost Disease, 1992-2004; 3 folders (Box 25)
      Research materials on the cost disease
    - Cost Disease Background Materials, 1993 (Box 76)
    - Cost Disease in Education, 2011 (Box 76)
    - Current Problems, 1962-1966; undated (Box 79)
      Includes notes on costs of borrowing, discount factors, and models of price cycles
    - Data for graphs, 1988-1989; 10 document (Lotus 1-2-3 format) and still image (HP Vector Graphic) files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0084)
    - Data for research, 1983; 4 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0120)
    - Data for research, 1983; 7 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0121)
    - Data for research, 1988; 5 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0043)
    - Data for research, 1987-1988; 15 document file (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0049)
    - Data for research, 1987-1988; 8 document file (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0053)
    - Data for research, 1980-1987; 45 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0021)
    - Diagrams for research, 1989; 4 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0050)
    - Diagrams on Portfolio Analysis, undated (Box 32)
    - Downsizing Memos, 1998 (Box 76)
      Includes materials on downsizing trends in manufacturing
    - Economic History, 1969-1986; 4 folders (Box 13)
      Includes files for research on economic history
    - Education, 2006; 2 folders (Box 76)
      Includes materials for research on education
    - Education and Entrepreneurship, 2004-2006 (Box 34)
      Includes research materials and related correspondence
    - Entrepreneurship, 2001 (Box 76)
    - Entrepreneurship, 2004-2005; undated; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Notes research materials on entrepreneurship research
    - Entrepreneurship and Education, 1961-2007; 5 folders (Box 76)
    - Entrepreneurship and Education, 1994-2006; undated; 4 folders (Box 81)
    - Entrepreneurship and Education, undated (Box 32)
      Research materials on entrepreneurship at top business schools
    - Entrepreneurship and Growth, 2000-2007; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Entrepreneurship History, 2004-2009; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Entrepreneurship: Micro Theory, 2005-2010; 4 folders (Box 76)
    - Entrepreneurship: Small Firms, 2003-2005 (Box 76)
    - Equity Ownership in Joint Ventures, 2005; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Existence Proof: Exchange Model, undated (Box 76)
      Includes notes on proof of existence of general equilibrium model with exchange
    - Fairness, 1964-1984; undated (Box 78)
      Includes reference materials on theories of fairness and distributive justice
    - Files for charts and graphs, 1987; 8 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0010)
    - Files for charts and graphs, 1980-1987; 14 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0011)
    - Files for charts and graphs, 1987; 15 document files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0012)
    - Files for graphs, 1983-1986; 7 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0085)
    - Files for graphs and images, 1983-1987; 24 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 and unidentified formats); less than 1 MB (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0019)
    - Files for graphs and images used in research, 1987; 2 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0096)
    - Files for graphs and images with supporting data, 1983; 14 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0023)
    - Files for graphs and supporting data, 1985-1988; 83 document, still image, and unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0082)
    - Files for graphs and supporting data, 1988-1989; 50 document (Lotus 1-2-3 format) and still image (HP Vector Graphic format) files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0086)
    - Files for images and supporting data, 1980-1987; 11 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0017)
    - Finance, 1965-1986 (Box 79)
      Includes reference materials on asset pricing models
    - Finland, undated (Box 76)
      Includes notes on the history of Finland
    - Futureworld, 2007-2010; 2 folders (Box 77)
      Includes research materials on health care expenditures
    - Good Cap., Bad Cap., 2006 (Box 77)
      Includes materials on environmental issues
    - Growth, 1990-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Growth and Catch-up in Central and Eastern Europe, 1992 (Box 32)
    - History of Economic Ideas, 1974-2002; 3 folders (Box 77)
    - History of Economics, 1972-1986; undated; 11 folders (Box 80)
      Includes notes and research materials on prominent figures in the history of economics, such as Cantillon, Cournot, Marshall, Marx, Ricardo, Robbins, Smith, and Wicksell
    - History of Economics: Marx, Karl, 1972-1973; undated (Box 83)
      Includes articles about Marx's ideas
    - Image files for writings, 1989; 9 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0055)
    - Image files for writings, 1990; 9 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0032)
    - Induced Technical Change, 2006 (Box 32)
    - Industrial Organization, 1975-1985; undated; 7 folders (Box 80)
      Includes notes and research materials on contestability and predatory pricing
    - Innovation and Technology, 2002 (Box 32)
    - Innovative Medicine - remote surgery, etc., 2005 (Box 77)
    - International Health Care Costs, 1994-2001 (Box 77)
    - Inventions and Inventors, 1989-2006; 6 folders (Box 32)
      Includes research materials on the history of significant inventions and inventors
    - Inventor and Entrepreneurship Project, 2005-2006; 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Inventors Lists, 2004 (Box 77)
    - Investment and GNP data, 1989; 1 document (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0039)
    - Japan and US Productivity Project, 1987 (Box 32)
      Includes correspondence and research materials
    - Lazarsfeld Project, 1953 (Box 77)
      Includes research materials on statistical methods
    - Marxian Economics, 1952-1998 (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous Figures and Diagrams, undated (Box 77)
      Includes figures and diagrams used in research
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 32)
      Unlabeled hand-written notes
    - Mozart, 1991; 3 folders (Box 79)
      Includes files for research on Mozart and the economics of music in Vienna
    - Mozart, 1992; undated; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Research materials on Mozart and the economics of music during his time
    - Music in Vienna, undated (Box 32)
      Research materials on the economics of music in Vienna during the 19th century
    - Musicians, 1997 (Box 32)
      Research materials on musicians
    - Natural Resources, 2006 (Box 32)
      Research materials on petroleum prices and use of natural resources
    - Nobel Laureates, 2006 (Box 77)
      Includes background information for project on Nobel laureates
    - Nonlinear Differential Equations, 1984 (Box 79)
    - Patents, 2005-2009; undated (Box 77)
    - Patents, undated (Box 32)
    - Performing Arts, 1966-1993; undated; 10 folders (Box 18)
      Includes files for research on the economics of the performing arts
    - Performing Arts, 1981 (Box 24)
      Includes research materials related to West End Theatre of London
    - Performing Arts, 1970-1985; undated; 7 folders (Box 17)
      Includes research materials on ticket prices, costs, and salaries, among other items, for the performing arts
    - Performing Arts and Economics, 1966-1990; 15 folders (Box 81)
      Includes notes and research materials for project on funding performing arts and understanding the market for performing arts
    - Performing Arts and Economics: Financial Data, 1975-1981 (Box 83)
    - Portfolio Theory, 1963-1969 (Box 79)
    - Possible Merger Study, 1998-2003 (Box 68)
      Includes materials for potential research project with Burton Malkiel
    - PPP Notes, 2004 (Box 68)
      Includes research materials on purchasing power parity
    - Productivity, 1985-2007; 2 folders (Box 81)
      Includes research materials on productivity growth
    - Productivity, 1980-1985; 8 folders (Box 13)
      Includes files for research on productivity growth
    - Productivity and Growth, 2002-2006 (Box 24)
    - Productivity Graphs, 1985; undated; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Various graphs used for research on productivity growth over multiple projects
    - Productivity Project Questionnaires, 1986 (Box 32)
    - Productivity, R and D, Education, 1983 (Box 32)
      Includes data and graphs for project on productivity
    - Productivity/Entrepreneurship, 1975-1986; undated; 3 folders (Box 79)
      Includes reference materials on productivity growth and entrepreneurship
    - Productivity/Entrepreneurship, 1965-1993; undated; 8 folders (Box 79)
    - Puerto Rico, 2009-2010 (Box 68)
      Includes materials for research on productivity growth in Puerto Rico
    - Puerto Rico, 2010 (Box 32)
      Research materials on productivity growth in Puerto Rico
    - Puerto Rico Growth Project, 1986 (Box 32)
      Includes draft proposal
    - Quotes, 1980-2009 (Box 68)
      Includes unsorted materials to quote from
    - Quotes, 2007; undated (Box 32)
      Includes various printouts of writings that Baumol used for quotations
    - Red Queen Game, undated (Box 23)
      Includes notes
    - RGDPART, undated (Box 68)
      Includes unsorted data tables for projects
    - Ricardo and Say, 1975-2009 (Box 34)
      Includes materials for research related to ideas of David Ricardo and Jean Baptiste Say
    - Scottish Economic Performance, 2003; 3 folders (Box 30)
      Includes research materials on productivity, technology, education, and growth in Scotland
    - Serra, undated (Box 79)
      Includes translation of a piece of writing by Antonio Serra
    - Some Suggested Institutional Circumstances that Have Invited Unproductive (Redistributive) Entrepreneurial Activity, 2007 (Box 34)
    - South Korea, 2012 (Box 34)
    - Stock Options, undated (Box 32)
      Includes research materials on stock options as part of compensation packages
    - Study of New York Theatre, 1966-1972 (Box 18)
      Includes files for research on New York City theatre facilitated by the mayor's office
    - Sue Anne Batey Blackman's Files on Productivity, 1978-1984; 4 folders (Box 13)
      Includes files kept by Sue Anne Batey Blackman on productivity for her research with Baumol
    - Technological Progress and Growth, 2001-2002 (Box 23)
    - Technology Transfer Miscellaneous Materials, 1985-1987 (Box 34)
    - Unemployment, 1996-1999; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Wages, 1973-1985 (Box 32)
      Includes research materials on international wages
    - World Bank Reports, 1991 (Box 32)
      Includes data from World Bank reports
  - Writings by Others, 1953-2009 and undated; 2
    This subseries contains a portion academic writings by others used in Baumol's research. Files are grouped by last name of the author in most instances and by subject in others.
    - A, 1982; undated (Box 30)
    - A, 1990-2002 (Box 33)
    - B, undated (Box 30)
    - B, 1958-1993 (Box 33)
    - C, 1953; 2007 (Box 30)
    - C, 1993-1996 (Box 33)
    - Cost Disease, 2001-2003; 4 folders (Box 39)
      Includes various writings by others on Baumol's theory of the cost disease
    - D, 1960; undated (Box 30)
    - D, 1992-2000 (Box 33)
    - Deceleration of British Growth (1973-1913) by Arthur Lewis, 1967 (Box 36)
    - E, 2009; undated (Box 30)
    - E, 1979-1993 (Box 33)
    - F, 1990-2005; 4 folders (Box 33)
    - Fox, Eleanor, 2002 (Box 36)
    - G, 1989-1997 (Box 33)
    - H, 1963 (Box 30)
    - H, 1953-1997 (Box 33)
    - I, 1991 (Box 33)
    - J, 2003 (Box 30)
    - J, 1995-1998 (Box 33)
    - K, undated (Box 30)
    - K, 1979-1992; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - L, 2007; undated (Box 30)
    - L, 1991-2003 (Box 33)
    - M, 1980-1987; undated (Box 30)
    - M, undated (Box 33)
    - Moore, Julia, 1992; 4 folders (Box 36)
    - Moynihan, D.P., Baumol's Cost Disease, 1993 (Box 36)
    - N, 1973; 1997 (Box 30)
    - N, 1980-1997; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - New York Review of Books, 2006 (Box 36)
    - O, 2000 (Box 30)
    - O, 1996-2002 (Box 33)
    - P, 1980-2004 (Box 30)
    - P, 1992-2006 (Box 33)
    - Q, 1994 (Box 39)
    - R, 2008; undated (Box 39)
    - R, 1986-1994 (Box 33)
    - S, 1981-2003; undated; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Scholarly writings by others, 2000-2007; 3808 document files (PDF format); approximately 700 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-OP-0003)
    - Scholarly writings by others, 2003-2006; 3808 document files (PDF format); approximately 700 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-OP-0004)
    - Select Committee on Economic Affairs, House of Lords, 2003 (Box 36)
    - Shapiro, Carl, 2001; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - T, 1979-2009; undated; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - U, undated (Box 39)
    - U, V, 1980-1992 (Box 39)
    - V, 1986-1988 (Box 39)
    - Varian, Hal, 2001-2002 (Box 39)
    - W, 2003; undated (Box 39)
    - Wolff, Edward - "Capital Formation and Long-Term Productivity Growth: A Comparison of Seven Countries", undated; 2 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0067)
    - W, X, Y, Z, 1979-2006; undated (Box 39)
    - Z, undated (Box 39)
- Writings, 1946-2012 and undated
  This series contains copies, reprints, drafts, notes, other documents, and correspondence associated with Baumol's published works. These include: reprints, copies, and drafts of published journal articles and book chapters; copies of books authored by Baumol, as well as drafts for various book projects; and documents from his referee activity for academic journals and publishers. Additional correspondence can be found in the Correspondence and Research and Notes series.
  - Articles, Book Chapters, and Other Papers, 1946-2012 and undated; 1
    Contains copies, reprints, and drafts of Baumol's published journal articles, chapters contributed to edited volumes, and unpublished papers.
    - A Conversation with Will Baumol on Capitalism, Innovation and Growth, 2003 (Box 45)
      Reprint
    - A Country's Maximal Gains from Trade and Conflicting National Interests, 1998 (Box 34)
      Working paper
    - A Dialogue With William J. Baumol: Insights on Entrepreneurial Theory and Education, 2007 (Box 45)
    - A Glimpse of the Invisible Hand, 1990 (Box 2)
      Draft
    - A key role for input-output analysis in policy design, 1991 (Box 1)
    - A Millennium of Economics in 20 Minutes: In Pursuit of Useful Knowledge, 1999 (Box 25)
    - A Millennium of Economics in 20 Minutes: In Pursuit of Useful Knowledge, 1999 (Box 29)
      Copy
    - A Millennium of Economics in 20 Minutes: In Pursuit of Useful Knowledge, 1999 (Box 45)
    - A Modest Decline isn't all that bad, 1987 (Box 6)
      Copy of article for New York Times
    - A New Rationale for Corporate Social Policy, 1970 (Box 45)
    - A note on Fiscal Illusion and the Cost Disease, 1991 (Box 2)
    - A Paradox in the Measurement of Interindustry Differences in Productivity, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Drafts and related materials
    - A Paradox in the Measurement of Interindustry Differences in Productivity, 1982 (Box 45)
      Drafts
    - A Point-Counterpoint on Stranded Cost for Pub. Util. Fort., 1995 (Box 45)
    - A test for burden for regulation of rates, 1973 (Box 17)
      Drafts and notes
    - A Theory of Speculation Relating Profitability and Stability, 1959 (Box 45)
    - A Warehouse Location Problem, 1958 (Box 45)
    - Acceleration Incentives and X Efficiency, undated (Box 17)
    - Acceleration Without Magnification, 1956 (Box 45)
    - Activity Analysis in One Lesson, 1958 (Box 45)
      Drafts, reprints, correspondence
    - Adam Smith that Nobody Knows, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Allocation of Costs n a Joint Product, undated (Box 84)
    - Alternative Interest Theories in Disequilibrium Conditions, 1959 (Box 45)
    - An Analysis of Alternative Policies for Attaining and Maintaining a Short-term NO2 Standard, 1979 (Box 38)
    - An Essay on the Sources and Nature of Entrepreneurial Profit, undated (Box 45)
    - An Expected Gain-Confidence Limit Criterion for Portfolio Selection, 1963; undated; 2 folders (Box 45)
      Reprint and galley proofs
    - An Interview with William J. Baumol, 2001 (Box 26)
    - An Interview with William J. Baumol, 2001 (Box 45)
    - An Inventory Theoretic Model of Freight Transport Demand, 1970 (Box 45)
    - Analogy Between Producer and Consumer Equilibrium Analysis, 1950 (Box 45)
    - Analyse Graphique de Modeles de Cycles Non Lineaire de Premier Ordre, 1956 (Box 45)
    - Analysis of linear trade models and relation to scale economies, 1997 (Box 45)
    - Analysis of Public Policy in Dynamic Urban Models, 1971 (Box 45)
    - Analyzing the Growth Miracle of the Free-Market Economies, 2003 (Box 45)
    - Annual Report of the Economic Policy Council of New Jersey, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Anti-trust Policy and High Technology Industries, 1988 (Box 45)
      Copy and correspondence
    - Antitrust: Source of Dynamic and Static Inefficiencies, 1990; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Antitrust: Source of Dynamic and Static Inefficiencies?, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Antitrust: Source of Dynamic and Static Inefficiencies?, Undated (Box 25)
    - Article for Soc. Sci. Encycl., 2003 (Box 45)
    - Artistic Deficit: The Constraints that Circumscribe Artistic Choice, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Arts in the "New Economy", 2003 (Box 24)
      Includes drafts, research materials, and related correspondence
    - Arts in the "New Economy", 2003; 2 folders (Box 45)
      Drafts, research materials, and correspondence
    - Automobile Industry in the World Market, Undated (Box 25)
    - Bernoulli Translation, 1954 (Box 45)
      Drafts and correspondence
    - Broadway data and papers, 1980-1987; 9 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 and HP Vector Graphic formats); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0015)
    - Business Morality and the Social Interest: Smith vs Marx, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Business Responsibility and Economic Behavior, 1972-1973 (Box 45)
    - Calculation of Optimal Product and Retailer Characteristics, 1967 (Box 45)
      Reprints
    - Capitalism: Growth Miracle Maker, Growth Saboteur, 2007 (Box 25)
    - Cardinal Utility Which is Ordinal, 1958; 2 folders (Box 45)
      Drafts, reprint, and correspondence
    - Carteis tecnologicos, 1991 (Box 45)
    - Catching up in the Postwar Period: Puerto Rico as the Fifth "Tiger", 1996 (Box 45)
    - Changes in the World Economy and Economics Education, 1990 (Box 2)
    - Chaos Models and their Implications for Forecasting, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Chaos models and their implications for forecasting (reprint), 1995 (Box 36)
    - Chaos Phenomenon: A Nightmare for Forecasters, 1986; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Chaos Phenomenon: A Nightmare for Forecasters, 1986 (Box 17)
      Draft and research materials
    - Chaos Theory Survey Article, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1980; 4 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0057)
      Files for paper on chaos with Jess Benhabib.
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1987; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 45)
      Drafts and reprint
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1987; 6 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0058)